<ad_break>
    <advert>
        <unique_id>AMVMWMT059020</unique_id>
        <brand>Mars maltesers</brand>
        <duration_seconds>20</duration_seconds>
        <last_timecode>02:03</last_timecode>
        <description>The Maltesers product packaging and tagline &quot;Look on the light side&quot; are visible in the final frames before the channel transition/next ad.</description>
    </advert>
    <advert>
        <unique_id>HOGHZBE665020</unique_id>
        <brand>Heinz baked beans</brand>
        <duration_seconds>20</duration_seconds>
        <last_timecode>02:22</last_timecode>
        <description>The Heinz logo and slogan &quot;BEANZ MEANZ HEINZ&quot; appear prominently. The ad concludes with text overlays before transitioning to the next commercial.</description>
    </advert>
    <advert>
        <unique_id>BURTBUT070010</unique_id>
        <brand>Butlins holiday worlds drtv</brand>
        <duration_seconds>10</duration_seconds>
        <last_timecode>02:33</last_timecode>
        <description>The Butlins Big Weekenders logo and text appear over footage of a nightclub event, fading out just before the next animated commercial starts.</description>
    </advert>
    <advert>
        <unique_id>HASFCPA002030</unique_id>
        <brand>Fast cash property</brand>
        <duration_seconds>30</duration_seconds>
        <last_timecode>03:03</last_timecode>
        <description>Animated graphics illustrating fast property sales conclude with contact information and the promise of &quot;7 DAYS&quot; sale.</description>
    </advert>
    <advert>
        <unique_id>HOGSKSH891020</unique_id>
        <brand>Skechers sport shoes</brand>
        <duration_seconds>20</duration_seconds>
        <last_timecode>03:24</last_timecode>
        <description>The &quot;Hands Free Slip-ins&quot; promotional text is displayed alongside Jamie Redknapp demonstrating the shoes. The ad ends with a static shot of the shoe before the next spot begins.</description>
    </advert>
    <advert>
        <unique_id>TTBGSVO075020</unique_id>
        <brand>Voltarol pain relief</brand>
        <duration_seconds>20</duration_seconds>
        <last_timecode>03:43</last_timecode>
        <description>The Voltarol product tube and box are shown during the narrative of a cyclist. The Haleon brand logo (owner) appears in the final seconds before the next ad intro.</description>
    </advert>
    <advert>
        <unique_id>TJUIDHS092030</unique_id>
        <brand>Media 10 ideal home show</brand>
        <duration_seconds>30</duration_seconds>
        <last_timecode>04:13</last_timecode>
        <description>The Ideal Home Show promotional graphic featuring celebrity hosts remains on screen as the closing frame of this advertisement block.</description>
    </advert>
    <advert>
        <unique_id>WPNALIL065060</unique_id>
        <brand>Age uk weekly lottery</brand>
        <last_timecode>05:14</last_timecode>
        <description>The Age UK Play lottery banner and call-to-action overlay remain on screen throughout the ad, concluding just as a new commercial spot about fitness/energy drinks begins at 05:15.</description>
    </advert>
</ad_break>